# Leke Peter Abiodun

Full-stack Web Developer

lekepeterabiodun@gmail.com

+234 706 2427 397

Nigeria.

## **Summary**

I'm a dedicated and passionate Full-stack Web Developer with 3+ years of experience in web application development in both frontend and backend development, using PHP/Laravel/Livewire, WordPress, JavaScript/AlpineJS, Bootstrap/TailwindCSS. I'm willing and currently learning to master VueJS for single-page applications (SPA) and hybrid mobile apps.

## **Work Experience**

IT Assistant at Lagos State University.

Nigeria - Jun 2015 - Dec 2015

- Developed a WordPress-based eCommerce store.
- Developed a WordPress-based blog site.

#### Freelance WordPress Developer at WebSolutionsDublin.

Ireland - Feb 2017 - Oct 2018

- Design and development of multiple business websites.
- Design and development of landing pages for WebSolutionsDublin and clients.
- $\bullet$  Developedawebscrapertoautomatemostpartofthedata collectionin the company CRM.
- Created a few videos for marketing and promotions.

### Full-stack Developer at AppTech Solutions.

- Developed several modules for the in-house design of a school management system using PHP/Laravel.
- Developed a recruitment exercise job portal.
- Developed Human Resource Management System.
- Created multiple website templates.

### Freelance PHP/Laravel Developer at GetServ.

India -March 2020 - Feb 2021

- Developed customer service chatbot using Laravel.
- Developed an interface to connect with WhatsApp chat API.
- Integrated the Chat-botbackendwithWhatsAppchatAPIwithWhatsAppaccount.

### **Education**

### Bachelor of Science in Computer Science

Adekunle Ajasin University of Akungba: 2012

- Relevant Coursework: OperatingSystems, Architecture, Linux/Unix
- Programming, UsabilityinWebsiteandSoftwareDesign.C, C++, C#,
- JavaFORTRAN, PythonProgramming, RelationalDatabaseDesign&
- SQL, Compiler construction.

### Professional Certification in Project Management

Obafemi Awolowo University: 2017 - 2018.

## My tools

- Editors: Sublime, VScode.
- Frameworks: Bootstrap, TailwindCSS, WordPress, Laravel, VueJS.
- Libraries: JQuery, Alpine, Laravel-Livewire.
- Languages: JavaScript, PHP, Python, MQL5.
- Database: MySQL.
- Version Control System: GIT.
- Project Management: Trello, Github.
- Testing Frameworks: PESTPHP, Cypress.

## Personal skills

- Good human skills, teamwork.
- $\bullet$  Fast learning, self-motivated.
- Analytical and precise in dealings with issues.
- $\bullet$  Verbal and written in English.
- $\bullet$  Conduct effective meetings using SCRUM.
- Google-Fu (I can search my way out of most technical problems).